Office of the Vice Provost Records UA166
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of the Vice Provost Records
1976 -- 2016
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of the Vice Provost
UA166
256.8 Linear Feet
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. The collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into three series: Funded grants, Boston Campus; Funded grants, Medford Campus; and 2017 accessions.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of the Vice Provost was formerly known as the Office of the Associate Provost for Research. Between November 1984 and July 1986 the positions of Director of Government Resources, Health Sciences, and the Director of Government Resources, Arts and Sciences, were moved from the University Development office to the Office of the Senior Vice President and Provost with the creation of the positions of Associate Provost for Research, Boston Campus and the Associate Provost for Research, Medford Campus. The two positions were combined during the 1993-1994 academic year, and the position was also expanded to include the Grafton campus. In 2004, the Associate Provost for Research became the Vice Provost.
Scope and Contents
These records consist of files related to funded grants consisting of, but not limited to: grant proposal narrative, budget, application form, and letters of support; notice of award from funding entity; Tufts Internal Notice of Award Form; Agreements/Contracts; F&A Tree Information Form; correspondence; no-Cost Extension Forms; progress and final reports; and Close Notices. These records primarily date from the mid 1980s onward. The function of these records is to document the process of funded grants at Tufts University. Materials are created by the grant applicants, related offices and departments, the Office of Research Administration and the Office of the Vice Provost. The Office of the Vice Provost is the holder of the official copy of these records.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Office of the Vice Provost, 2005-2017.
Research and Research Administration; Legal and Regulatory
- 2017 accessions, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA166.003; 46.8 Linear Feet
  Conditions Governing Access
  Records containing information related to student education, staff and faculty employment, and Board of Trustees records are closed for 75 years from the date of creation.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in order of accession.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains grant files for research completed on the Boston, Medford, and Grafton campuses between 1980 and 2016, as well as ORA Grant and Award files from FY12-FY14.
  - May 2017 accession, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.001; 13.2 Linear Feet 11 record cartons
    75 years from date of creation.
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by Jonathan Chau, Office of the Vice Provost, 2017, accession UA-2017-048.
    This series is arranged in received order.
    This series contains grant files for research completed on the Boston and Grafton campuses between 1980 and 1989, and document the funded grant process at Tufts University. Grant files may contain the grant proposal narrative, budget, application form, and letters of support; notice of award from funding entity; Tufts Internal Notice of Award Form; Agreements/Contracts; FandA Tree Information Form; correspondence; no-Cost Extension Forms; progress and final reports; and Close Notices. Materials are created by the grant applicants, related offices and departments, the Office of Research Administration and the Office of the Vice Provost. The Office of the Vice Provost is the holder of the official copy of these records.
    - Schwartz, Anthony: Travenol, SLE Dog Colony, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 1)
      75 years from the date of creation.
    - Stollar, David: Seragen, The Developmental, Investigational and Potential Uses of In-Vitro and In-Vivo Human-Human, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - Stollar, David: NSF, Immunochemical Studies of Nucleic Acids, Histones and Chromatin, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Ebert, Karl: Monsanto, Introduction, Expression and Regulation of Growth Promoting Genes in Swine, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Ebert, Karl: New England Medical Center, Ectopic Hormone Synthesis in Pochromocytoma Cells, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Ebert, Karl: Integrated Genetics, Production of Transgenic Mice which Secrete a Foreign Protein in Milk, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Dunlap, Kathleen: American Heart Association, Cyclic AMP and Transmitter Modulation of CA Channels, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Dwayer, Johanna: Stouffer, Diet and Serum Cholesterol Response in Aging Free Living Adults, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Drysdale, James: NIDDKD, Human Isoferritins Structure and Metabolism, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00009; 2 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 9-10)
    - Schwartz, Anthony: NIH, Response of Thymus Derived Cells to Antigen, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00010; 2 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 11-12)
    - Sawkat, Anwer: NIDDKD, Mechanism of Canalicular Bile Formation and Cholestasis, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00011; 3 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 13-15)
    - Levy, Stuart: Upjohn, Enhancement of the Effectiveness of Tetracycline Against Tetracycline Resistant Organisms, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 16)
    - Levy, Stuart: EPA, Molecular Biology, Pathogenicity and Ecology of Bacterial Plasmids, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 17)
    - Levy, Stuart: NSF, Compartmentalization of Plasmids in Escherichia Coli, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 18)
    - Levy, Stuart: American Cancer Society, Tetracycline Resistance: The Tetracycline Efflux System, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 19)
    - Libby, Peter: American Heart Association, Vascular Smooth Muscle Proteolysis: Comparing Pathways, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 20)
    - Libby, Peter: American Heart Association, Control of Growth and Vascular Wall Cells, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 21)
    - Libby, Peter: NIH, Relation of Proteolysis to Aortic Smooth Muscle Growth, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 22)
    - Lieberman, Judy: Whitaker Health Sciences Fund, Function of the Receptor in Lymphocyte Cytotoxicity, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 23)
    - Lipman, Ruth: NRSA, Lens Aging and the Ubiquitin Proteolytic System, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 24)
    - Lipman, Roth: Fight For Sight, Inc., Prevention of After-Cataract Formation, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 25)
    - Liscum, Laura: American Heart Association, CHO Cell Mutants in Intracellular Cholesterol Transport, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 26)
    - Liscum, Laura: Whitaker Health Sciences Fund, Biochemical and Genetic Analysis of Cholesterol Transport in Normal and Niemann-Pick Disease (Type C) Cells in Culture, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 27)
    - Loew, Franklin: NIH, Minority High School Student Research, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 28)
    - Loutan, Louis: USA for Africa, Health and Nutrition Monitoring: A Program for Faculty Development in Niger, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.169.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 169, Folder 29)
    - Low, Malcolm: Pfizer, Characterization of Tissue-Specific Regulatory Domains in the Rat Somatostatin Gene, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Ducibella, Thomas: NSF, Preimplantation Embryo Cell Surface Organization, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Hamburger, Robert: Veterans Administration, Evaluation of Clonidine TTS (Catapres TTS) Transdermal Therapeutic System for Mild to Moderate Hypertension, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Hamburger, Robert: Veterans Administration, The Effect of Dialyzer Membrane Compositon on Blood-Membrane Interaction, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Hartman, Ernest: NIDH, Alcohol Effects on Bruxism, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Madoff, Morton: HRSA-HHS, AHEC - Special Initiative, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00006; 3 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 6-8)
    - Madoff, Morton: NCHSR, Primary Prevention in Primary Care Practice Settings, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00007; 4 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 9-12)
    - Madoff, Morton: HRSA, Catalogue of Federal Domestic Assistance No. 13.824, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00008; 2 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 13-14)
    - Madoff, Morton: NIH, Improving Mammography Rates in Primary Care Practice, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 15)
    - Madoff, Morton: Band Aid, Niger Epidemiology Training Program, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 16)
    - Madoff, Morton: Division of Medicine/AHEC Branch, Tufts/Maine AHEC Special Initiative: Adolescent Pregnancy Education, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 17)
    - Susi, Frank: Area Health Education Center of Pioneer Valley, Dental Externship Program, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 18)
    - Ebert, Karl: Worcester Foundation for Experimental Biology, Expression of Preproenkephanlin-like mRNA in the Testis, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 19)
    - Ebert, Karl: American Cyanamid Company, Production of Transgenic Mice and Pigs, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 20)
    - Madoff, Morton: DHHS, Tufts/Maine Area Health Education Center, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 21)
    - Dunlap, Kathleen: McKnight Endowment Fund for Neuroscience, Direct Measurement of Calcium Influx into Electrophysiologically Inaccessible Nerve Terminals, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 22)
    - Schwartz, Anthony: Lowell General Hospital, Laparoscopic Cholecystectomy Courses for General Surgeons and Schwartz, Anthony: Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, Health Policy Fellowship Program, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 23)
    - Libby, Peter: American Heart Association, Paracrine and Autocrine Growth Control in the Vessel Wall, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 25)
    - Lichtenstein, Alice: American Heart Association, Omega-3 Fatty Acids, Atherosclerosis and the Watanabe rabbit, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 26)
    - Lindenmayer, Joann: The Medical Foundation, Inc., The threat of Lyme Disease: Increasing Prevalance or Increased Awareness?, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 27)
    - Loew, Franklin: DHHS, Scholarship for First Year Students of Exceptional Financial Need, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 28)
    - Loughna, Paul: DHHS, Muscle Fiber Atrophy, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 29)
    - Doku, Chris: Eli Lilley, Picenadol: Dose Response in Dental Pain, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 30)
    - Donahue, Rolfe: DHHS, Mechanisms of Action of Cholera Toxin, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 31)
    - Donaldson, William: Mass DPH, Orthopedic Services at Lemuel Shattuck, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 32)
    - Hamburger,: Mass DPH, Nephrology Services at Lemuel Shattuck, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 33)
    - Beck, Deborah: Whitaker Health Sciences Fund, How Does the Platelet Derived Factor-Receptor Complex Work?, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 34)
    - Barone, Leesa: Orthopaedic Research and Education Foundation, Characterization of Link Protein mRNA from Normal and Osteoarthritic Human Cartilage, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.170.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 170, Folder 35)
    - Baum, Jules: National Eye Institute, Biochemistry of Normal and Dystrophic Corneas, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00001; 3 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 1-3)
    - Birinyi, Louis: Whitaker Health Sciences Fund, Implantation of Prosthetic Vascular Grafts Containing Genetically Modified Endothelial Cells, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Biswas, Chritra: NCI, Mammalian Collagenase in Tumor Invasion, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Biswas, Chritra: NCI, Tumor Receptors for Heparin Sulfate, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00004; 2 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 6-7)
    - Troccoli, Noreen: American Cancer Society, Mechanisms of Host-Tumor Interactions in Tumor Invasion, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Blair, Henry: NIH, Preparation of Glucocerebrosidase from Human Placental Tissue, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00006; 3 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 9-11)
    - Blair, Henry: NIH, Preparation of Ceramidetrihexosidase from Human Placental Tissue, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00007; 2 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 12-13)
    - Blair, Murray: NIH, Biomedical Research Support Grant, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 14)
    - Bloomquist, Eunice: NIH, Smooth Muscle of Resistance Vessels in Hypertension, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 15)
    - Feig, Larry: Whitaker Health Sciences Fund, Ras-Related Rho and Rab Genes: Analysis of Dominant Inhibitory Mutants in S. Cerevisiae, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 16)
    - Feingold, David: NIH, Antifungal Drugs: Mechanisms and Treatment Implications, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 17)
    - Fister, Richard: Wyeth-Ayerst Research, In Vivo Absorption/Gastrointenstinal Studies of Two Antibacterial Agents, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 18)
    - Flax, Martin: Commonwealth of Massachusetts, Pathology Services at Soldiers' Home, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 19)
    - Fogels, Helmi: Lever Brothers, Flouride DentiFrice Study, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 20)
    - Forgac, Michael: American Heart Association, Characterization of the Coated Vesicle Proton Pump, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 21)
    - Fooks, Wanda: DHHS, Continuing Education for NHSC Dentists, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 22)
    - Fogels, Helmi: Pfizer, Leukotriene Substance P Interactions in the Airways, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 23)
    - Forgac, Michael: NIDDKD, GI Research on Absorptive and Secretory Processes, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00018; 2 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 24-25)
    - Forgac, Michael: NIH, Structure and Properties of the Coated Vesicle Cl Channel, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 26)
    - Gilmore, William: Sandoz Pharmaceuticals, Proquazone/Analgesia Study, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 27)
    - Gill, Michael: NIH, Function of Poly(ADP-Ribose), 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 28)
    - Gill, Michael: NIH, Mechanism of Action of Cholera Toxin, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00022; 2 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 29-30)
    - Goldberg, Edward: NIH, Multiuser Electron Microscope Facility, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 31)
    - Goldberg, Edward: NIH, Structure of Phage T4 Tail Fibers, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.171.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 171, Folder 32)
    - Goldberg, Robert: DHHS, Heart Attack Community Surveillance Study, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Goldberg, Robert: DHHS, Keep the Beat: A Heart Attack Intervention Program, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00002; 3 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 2-4)
    - Goldberg, Edward: BioTechnica International, Purification and Characterization of the Protein Determined by Gene 2 of Bacteriophage T4, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Goldberg, Harold: Public Health Service, Psychiatry - Basic Residency, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Goldberg, Ronald: Arthritis Foundation, Postdoctoral Fellowship, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Goldin, Barry: American Institute for Cancer Research, The Effect of Lactobacillus on Chemically Induced Colon Tumors in the Rat, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Goldin, Barry: USDA, Relationship Between Nutrition Factors and Cancers of the Breast and Colon in Hawaiian Americans, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Goldin, Barry: Valio, The Effect of Lactobacillius GG on Immunological and Inflammatory Responses, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - Goldman, Melvin:, Patent - Impregnation of Dentinal Tubules, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - Goldman, Melvin: Pain Suppression Labs, Research in Pain Suppression, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - Goldman, Melvin: Dentsply, Comparative Study of Root Canal Systems Instrumentation, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 13)
    - Goldspink, Geoffrey: NASA, The Combined Influence of Stretch, Mobility and Electrical Stimulation of the Prevention of Muscle Fiber Atrophy Caused by Hypokinesis and Hypodynamia, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 14)
    - Bachovchin, William: The University Hospital, IGA Protease and Dental Caries, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00013; 2 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 15-16)
    - Bachovchin, William: DHHS, Acquisition of NMR Spectrometer, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 17)
    - Bachovchin, William: NIDDKD, Nitrogen-15 & Carbon-13 NMR Studies of Serine Proteases, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 18)
    - Bachovchin, William: NIGMS, Structure, Dynamics & Mechanism of Serine Proteases, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00016; 2 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 19)
    - King, Joan: NIH, LH-RH Localization and Dynamics, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 20)
    - KIng, Joan: DHHS, Gonadotropin Releasing Hormone Dynamics and Behavior, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 21)
    - King, Joan: Abbot Laboratories, Estrogen Receptor Monoclonal Antibodies for Immunocytochemical Investigations of Hypothalmic Neurons, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 22)
    - Souroujon, Miriam: N/A, Rothschild Fellowship, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 23)
    - Kisluk, Roy: National Cancer Institute, Folate Enzymes, Coenzymes and Antimetabolites, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00021; 3 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 24-26)
    - Knudson, Warren: NIH, Hyaluronic Acid in Tumor Invasion, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 27)
    - Klein, Robert: NICHHD, New England Hypothyroidism Collaborative Follow-Up Study, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 28)
    - Koblick, Philip: Electro Biology Inc., Pulsed Electromagnetic Field Stimulation of Regional Blood Flow, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 29)
    - Stollar, David: DHHS, Immunochemical Basis for Inducing Tolerance to DNA, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.172.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 172, Folder 30)
    - Stollar, David: NIH, Hybridoma-Produced Antibodies - Systemic Lupus, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Stollar, David: NIAID, Monoclonal Human Lupus Antibodies, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Spiegelman, Donna: NIH, Measurement Errors in Cancer and Respiratory Epidemiology, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00003; 2 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 3-4)
    - Haley, Steven: CDC, Psychosocial Factors of Children's Recovery from Trauma, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00004; 2 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 5-6)
    - Haber, Jerome: NIH, Genetics of Antibodies to Periodontal Pathogens, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00005; 2 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 7-8)
    - Haber, Jerome: NIH, Immunological Studies - Caries and Periodontal Disease, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - Gustafson, Alvar: NSF, Plasma Sex Steroid-Binding Protein and Puberty in Males, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - Greenleaf, Robert: NIH, Conditions for Primary Culture of Adult Lung Cells, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - Greenblatt, David: Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Association Foundation, Dvelopment of a Clinical Pharmacologies Unit, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - Graziani, Andrea: American Heart Association, Purification and Gene Cloning of the Phosphatydilinositol Kinase, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - Gray, Mark: NIH, Mouse Genetic Markers Using Denaturing Gradient Gels, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 14)
    - Hartmann, Ernest: NIDA, L-typtophan: A hypnotic agent with no abuse potential, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - Hartmann, Ernest: FDA Office of Orphan Product Development, Typtophan Treatment for Alcohol-Related Insomnia, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00013; 2 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 16-17)
    - Serunian, Leslie: NIH, Phosphatidylinositol Phosphate Kinase + Transformation, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 18)
    - Shader, Richard: DHHS, Applications of Pharmacokinetics in Clinical Psychiatry, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00015; 5 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 19-23)
    - Gaasch, William: NHLBI, Myocardial Relaxation and LV Diastolic Compliance, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 24)
    - Gaasch, William: AHA, Mechanical Effects of an Aneurysm on LV Relaxation and Gaasch, William: AHA, Myocardial pH During Ischemia in LV Hypertrophy, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 25)
    - Gavin, William: Department of Heath, Education & Welfare, Residency Program in General Internal Medicine, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00018; 2 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 26-27)
    - Gelfand, Jeffrey: NIH, Burn Injury and Shock: The Role of Compliment, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 28)
    - Gelfand, Jeffrey: NIH, Pathobiology of Intravenous Lipid Emulsions in Children, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.173.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 173, Folder 29)
    - Gershoff, Stanley: USDA, Research on Nutrition as it Affects Aging, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Gilchrest, Barbara: NCI, Retinoids and UV-Induced Melanogenesis, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 2)